<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Some Testfeed</title><link>https://www.econdiy.wiki/</link><description>Description of your podcast</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 13:44:04 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>jpe/JPE_CN_Volume 132, Number 6</title><description>none</description><content:encoded>输 老年人意识到他们的认知能力下降了吗？误解与财务决策   再分配分配机制   家庭生产中未观察到的投入   住房供应的微观地理学   套利的价值   企业职业：能力学习与人力资本获取的作用   外债、资本管制和二级市场：来自纳粹德国的理论和证据   儿童保育市场、父母劳动力供应和儿童发展   JPE周转时间   最近的裁判       01         老年人意识到他们的认知能力下降了吗？误解与财务决策         作者 |     Fabrizio Mazzonna and Franco Peracchi    摘要 |           我们调查了老年人是否正确地感知了他们的认知能力下降以及误解的潜在经济后果。首先，我们发现老年人往往低估了他们的认知能力下降。然后我们发现，那些经历了严重衰退但没有意识到的人更有可能遭受财富损失。这些损失在很大程度上反映了金融财富的减少，主要是以前活跃在股市上的富人所经历的。我们的研究结果支持这样一种观点，即没有意识到自己认知能力下降的老年人的经济损失是糟糕的财务决策的结果，而不是理性的撤资策略。         02         再分配分配机制         作者 |     Mohammad Akbarpour, Piotr Dworczak, and Scott Duke Kominers    摘要 |           许多稀缺的公共资源是以低于市场结算价格分配的，有时是免费的。这种“非市场”机制牺牲了一些盈余，但它们有可能提高公平性。我们开发了一个具有再分配关注的机制设计模型。代理商的特点是私下观察到的为质量付费的意愿、公开观察到的标签和社会福利权重。市场设计者控制一组异质质量对象的分配和定价，并最大化福利函数的期望。设计者没有直接观察个人的社会福利权重。我们得出了关于最优机制形式的结构性见解，从而形成了一个确定如何以及何时使用非市场机制的框架。         03         家庭生产中未观察到的投入         作者 |     Sergey Mityakov and Thomas A. Mroz    摘要 |           大多数家庭生产研究忽略了未观察到的投入。然而，如果没有额外的假设，由于未观测到的投入的污染变化，观测到的输入的估计影响无法提供边际产品的信息估计。甚至连边际影响的迹象都无法确定。通过在分析中包括有关非生产性（纯消费）商品的详细信息，可以确定这些偏差的方向，并显著减少偏差。先前需求研究的估计也有助于确定偏差的方向。我们描述了在缺乏此类额外信息的情况下必须援引的严格假设，以便能够将估计的影响与真实的边际产品联系起来。         04         住房供应的微观地理学         作者 |     Nathaniel Baum-Snow and Lu Han    摘要 |           我们对住房供应进行了全面的邻里层面分析。使用我们的估计对美国所有城市社区的占地面积和住房单位供应弹性的预测平均为0.5和0.3，显示出城市内部比城市之间更大的变化。新建工程约占单位供应响应的50%，在拆除和翻新方面发挥着重要的额外作用。供应反应随着中央商务区的发展而增长，主要是与未开发土地、平坦土地和较少监管的日益增加相距甚远。识别来自通勤目的地劳动力需求冲击的变化，这是使用定量空间平衡模型的见解进行汇总的。         05         套利的价值         作者 |     Eduardo Dávila, Daniel Graves, and Cecilia Parlatore    摘要 |           本文研究了金融市场收盘价差的社会价值。我们证明了套利缺口恰好对应于执行套利交易的边际社会价值。此外，套利缺口和价格影响指标足以计算弥合套利缺口的总社会价值，套利缺口可能因不同原因出现，包括持有特定资产的非货币利益。理论上，我们表明，对于给定的套利缺口，在流动性更强的市场中，套利的总社会价值更高。我们计算了弥补利率平价违规的套利缺口所带来的福利收益。         06         企业职业：能力学习与人力资本获取的作用         作者 |     Elena Pastorino    摘要 |           工作和工资的流动性可能源于公司和工人对工人能力的了解，也可能源于工人获得有经验的人力资本。迄今为止，这两个机制的相对重要性一直存在争议。使用一家公司的管理数据，我估计了一个将它们整合在一起的结构模型。我发现现有工作所关注的关于能力的信念对工资的直接影响很小。然而，通过改进员工对公司工作的分类，了解能力间接成为工资增长和分散的关键决定因素。         07         外债、资本管制和二级市场：来自纳粹德国的理论和证据         作者 |     Andrea Papadia and Claudio A. Schioppa    摘要 |           我们研究了内部分配动机如何影响一项重要宏观经济政策的实施：资本控制。为了做到这一点，我们研究了20世纪30年代德国在严格的资本控制下发生的历史上最大的债务遣返之一，提供了丰富的数量和历史证据。我们表明，当局严格控制私人遣返，从而避免了不利的宏观经济影响，同时允许自由遣返，以获得内部政治利益。我们在一个模型中正式化了这一机制，在该模型中，精英捕获可以影响资本控制下的最佳债务遣返和官方储备管理。         08         儿童保育市场、父母劳动力供应和儿童发展         作者 |     Samuel Berlinski, Maria Marta Ferreyra, Luca Flabbi, and Juan David Martin    摘要 |           我们开发并估计了儿童保育的供需模型。在需求方面，家庭做出消费、劳动力供应和育儿的决定。在供应方面，中心做出准入、价格和质量决策。此外，还提供带薪和非正式护理人员。儿童的发展取决于与父母和非租赁护理提供者相处的时间。我们使用来自幼儿纵向研究、出生队列的数据来估计模型，并进行政策实验。只有在高质量的中心或在职母亲才能使用的代金券尤其有效，因为它们在增加母亲劳动力供应的同时，还能促进儿童发展。    </content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.econdiy.wiki/jpe/JPE_CN_Volume 132, Number 60009</guid></item><item><title>jpe/JPE_CN_Volume 132, Number 6</title><description>none</description><content:encoded>输 老年人意识到他们的认知能力下降了吗？误解与财务决策   再分配分配机制   家庭生产中未观察到的投入   住房供应的微观地理学   套利的价值   企业职业：能力学习与人力资本获取的作用   外债、资本管制和二级市场：来自纳粹德国的理论和证据   儿童保育市场、父母劳动力供应和儿童发展   JPE周转时间   最近的裁判       01         老年人意识到他们的认知能力下降了吗？误解与财务决策         作者 |     Fabrizio Mazzonna and Franco Peracchi    摘要 |           我们调查了老年人是否正确地感知了他们的认知能力下降以及误解的潜在经济后果。首先，我们发现老年人往往低估了他们的认知能力下降。然后我们发现，那些经历了严重衰退但没有意识到的人更有可能遭受财富损失。这些损失在很大程度上反映了金融财富的减少，主要是以前活跃在股市上的富人所经历的。我们的研究结果支持这样一种观点，即没有意识到自己认知能力下降的老年人的经济损失是糟糕的财务决策的结果，而不是理性的撤资策略。         02         再分配分配机制         作者 |     Mohammad Akbarpour, Piotr Dworczak, and Scott Duke Kominers    摘要 |           许多稀缺的公共资源是以低于市场结算价格分配的，有时是免费的。这种“非市场”机制牺牲了一些盈余，但它们有可能提高公平性。我们开发了一个具有再分配关注的机制设计模型。代理商的特点是私下观察到的为质量付费的意愿、公开观察到的标签和社会福利权重。市场设计者控制一组异质质量对象的分配和定价，并最大化福利函数的期望。设计者没有直接观察个人的社会福利权重。我们得出了关于最优机制形式的结构性见解，从而形成了一个确定如何以及何时使用非市场机制的框架。         03         家庭生产中未观察到的投入         作者 |     Sergey Mityakov and Thomas A. Mroz    摘要 |           大多数家庭生产研究忽略了未观察到的投入。然而，如果没有额外的假设，由于未观测到的投入的污染变化，观测到的输入的估计影响无法提供边际产品的信息估计。甚至连边际影响的迹象都无法确定。通过在分析中包括有关非生产性（纯消费）商品的详细信息，可以确定这些偏差的方向，并显著减少偏差。先前需求研究的估计也有助于确定偏差的方向。我们描述了在缺乏此类额外信息的情况下必须援引的严格假设，以便能够将估计的影响与真实的边际产品联系起来。         04         住房供应的微观地理学         作者 |     Nathaniel Baum-Snow and Lu Han    摘要 |           我们对住房供应进行了全面的邻里层面分析。使用我们的估计对美国所有城市社区的占地面积和住房单位供应弹性的预测平均为0.5和0.3，显示出城市内部比城市之间更大的变化。新建工程约占单位供应响应的50%，在拆除和翻新方面发挥着重要的额外作用。供应反应随着中央商务区的发展而增长，主要是与未开发土地、平坦土地和较少监管的日益增加相距甚远。识别来自通勤目的地劳动力需求冲击的变化，这是使用定量空间平衡模型的见解进行汇总的。         05         套利的价值         作者 |     Eduardo Dávila, Daniel Graves, and Cecilia Parlatore    摘要 |           本文研究了金融市场收盘价差的社会价值。我们证明了套利缺口恰好对应于执行套利交易的边际社会价值。此外，套利缺口和价格影响指标足以计算弥合套利缺口的总社会价值，套利缺口可能因不同原因出现，包括持有特定资产的非货币利益。理论上，我们表明，对于给定的套利缺口，在流动性更强的市场中，套利的总社会价值更高。我们计算了弥补利率平价违规的套利缺口所带来的福利收益。         06         企业职业：能力学习与人力资本获取的作用         作者 |     Elena Pastorino    摘要 |           工作和工资的流动性可能源于公司和工人对工人能力的了解，也可能源于工人获得有经验的人力资本。迄今为止，这两个机制的相对重要性一直存在争议。使用一家公司的管理数据，我估计了一个将它们整合在一起的结构模型。我发现现有工作所关注的关于能力的信念对工资的直接影响很小。然而，通过改进员工对公司工作的分类，了解能力间接成为工资增长和分散的关键决定因素。         07         外债、资本管制和二级市场：来自纳粹德国的理论和证据         作者 |     Andrea Papadia and Claudio A. Schioppa    摘要 |           我们研究了内部分配动机如何影响一项重要宏观经济政策的实施：资本控制。为了做到这一点，我们研究了20世纪30年代德国在严格的资本控制下发生的历史上最大的债务遣返之一，提供了丰富的数量和历史证据。我们表明，当局严格控制私人遣返，从而避免了不利的宏观经济影响，同时允许自由遣返，以获得内部政治利益。我们在一个模型中正式化了这一机制，在该模型中，精英捕获可以影响资本控制下的最佳债务遣返和官方储备管理。         08         儿童保育市场、父母劳动力供应和儿童发展         作者 |     Samuel Berlinski, Maria Marta Ferreyra, Luca Flabbi, and Juan David Martin    摘要 |           我们开发并估计了儿童保育的供需模型。在需求方面，家庭做出消费、劳动力供应和育儿的决定。在供应方面，中心做出准入、价格和质量决策。此外，还提供带薪和非正式护理人员。儿童的发展取决于与父母和非租赁护理提供者相处的时间。我们使用来自幼儿纵向研究、出生队列的数据来估计模型，并进行政策实验。只有在高质量的中心或在职母亲才能使用的代金券尤其有效，因为它们在增加母亲劳动力供应的同时，还能促进儿童发展。    </content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.econdiy.wiki/jpe/JPE_CN_Volume 132, Number 60008</guid></item><item><title>jpe/JPE_Volume 132, Number 6</title><description>none</description><content:encoded>输 Are Older People Aware of Their Cognitive Decline? Misperception and Financial Decision-Making   Redistributive Allocation Mechanisms   Unobserved Inputs in Household Production   The Microgeography of Housing Supply   The Value of Arbitrage   Careers in Firms: The Role of Learning about Ability and Human Capital Acquisition   Foreign Debt, Capital Controls, and Secondary Markets: Theory and Evidence from Nazi Germany   Childcare Markets, Parental Labor Supply, and Child Development   JPE Turnaround Times   Recent Referees       01         Are Older People Aware of Their Cognitive Decline? Misperception and Financial Decision-Making         作者 |     Fabrizio Mazzonna and Franco Peracchi    摘要 |           We investigate whether older people correctly perceive their cognitive decline and the potential financial consequences of misperception. First, we show that older people tend to underestimate their cognitive decline. We then show that those experiencing a severe decline but unaware of it are more likely to suffer wealth losses. These losses largely reflect decreases in financial wealth and are mainly experienced by wealthier people who were previously active on the stock market. Our findings support the view that financial losses among older people unaware of their cognitive decline are the result of bad financial decisions, not of rational disinvestment strategies.         02         Redistributive Allocation Mechanisms         作者 |     Mohammad Akbarpour, Piotr Dworczak, and Scott Duke Kominers    摘要 |           Many scarce public resources are allocated at below-market-clearing prices and sometimes for free. Such “nonmarket” mechanisms sacrifice some surplus, yet they can potentially improve equity. We develop a model of mechanism design with redistributive concerns. Agents are characterized by a privately observed willingness to pay for quality, a publicly observed label, and a social welfare weight. A market designer controls allocation and pricing of a set of objects of heterogeneous quality and maximizes the expectation of a welfare function. The designer does not directly observe individuals’ social welfare weights. We derive structural insights about the form of the optimal mechanism, leading to a framework for determining how and when to use nonmarket mechanisms.         03         Unobserved Inputs in Household Production         作者 |     Sergey Mityakov and Thomas A. Mroz    摘要 |           Most household production studies ignore unobserved inputs. Without additional assumptions, however, estimated impacts of the observed inputs cannot provide informative estimates of marginal products because of contaminating variations in unobserved inputs. Not even the signs of marginal impacts can be ascertained. One can establish the direction of these biases and significantly reduce them by including detailed information about nonproductive (pure consumption) goods in the analysis. Estimates from prior demand studies can also help determine the direction of the bias. We describe the stringent assumptions one must invoke in the absence of such additional information to be able to relate estimated effects to the true marginal products.         04         The Microgeography of Housing Supply         作者 |     Nathaniel Baum-Snow and Lu Han    摘要 |           We perform a comprehensive neighborhood-level analysis of housing supply. Predictions of floor space and housing unit supply elasticities using our estimates average 0.5 and 0.3 across all urban neighborhoods in the United States, exhibiting greater variation within than between metro regions. New construction accounts for about 50% of unit supply responses, with important additional roles for teardowns and renovations. Supply responses grow with central business district distance mostly from the increasing availability of undeveloped land, flatter land, and less regulation. Identification comes from variation in labor demand shocks to commuting destinations, as aggregated using insights from a quantitative spatial equilibrium model.         05         The Value of Arbitrage         作者 |     Eduardo Dávila, Daniel Graves, and Cecilia Parlatore    摘要 |           This paper studies the social value of closing price differentials in financial markets. We show that arbitrage gaps exactly correspond to the marginal social value of executing an arbitrage trade. Moreover, arbitrage gaps and price impact measures are sufficient to compute the total social value from closing an arbitrage gap, which may emerge for different reasons, including nonpecuniary benefits of holding particular assets. Theoretically, we show that, for a given arbitrage gap, the total social value of arbitrage is higher in more liquid markets. We compute the welfare gains from closing arbitrage gaps for covered interest parity violations.         06         Careers in Firms: The Role of Learning about Ability and Human Capital Acquisition         作者 |     Elena Pastorino    摘要 |           Job and wage mobility can arise from firms and workers learning about workers’ ability and from workers acquiring human capital with experience. To date, the relative importance of these two mechanisms is debated. Using administrative data from one firm, I estimate a structural model that integrates them. I find the direct effect of beliefs about ability on wages, which existing work has focused on, to be small. However, by improving the sorting of workers to the firm’s jobs, learning about ability is indirectly a crucial determinant of wage growth and dispersion.         07         Foreign Debt, Capital Controls, and Secondary Markets: Theory and Evidence from Nazi Germany         作者 |     Andrea Papadia and Claudio A. Schioppa    摘要 |           We investigate how internal distribution motives can affect the implementation of an important macroeconomic policy: capital controls. To do this, we study one of history’s largest debt repatriations, which took place under strict capital controls in 1930s Germany, providing a wealth of quantitative and historical evidence. We show that the authorities kept private repatriations under strict control, thus avoiding detrimental macroeconomic effects, while allowing discretionary repatriations in order to reap internal political benefits. We formalize this mechanism in a model in which elite capture can affect optimal debt repatriations and the management of official reserves under capital controls.         08         Childcare Markets, Parental Labor Supply, and Child Development         作者 |     Samuel Berlinski, Maria Marta Ferreyra, Luca Flabbi, and Juan David Martin    摘要 |           We develop and estimate a model of supply and demand for childcare. On the demand side, households make consumption, labor supply, and childcare decisions. On the supply side, centers make entry, price, and quality decisions. In addition, both paid and informal caregivers are available. Child development is a function of the time spent with parents and nonparental care providers. We estimate the model using data from the Early Childhood Longitudinal Study, Birth Cohort, and perform policy experiments. Vouchers that can be used only in high-quality centers or by working mothers are particularly effective, since they deliver child development gains while increasing mothers’ labor supply.    </content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.econdiy.wiki/jpe/JPE_Volume 132, Number 60007</guid></item><item><title>jpe/JPE_CN_Volume 132, Number 6</title><description>none</description><content:encoded>输 老年人意识到他们的认知能力下降了吗？误解与财务决策   再分配分配机制   家庭生产中未观察到的投入   住房供应的微观地理学   套利的价值   企业职业：能力学习与人力资本获取的作用   外债、资本管制和二级市场：来自纳粹德国的理论和证据   儿童保育市场、父母劳动力供应和儿童发展   JPE周转时间   最近的裁判       01         老年人意识到他们的认知能力下降了吗？误解与财务决策         作者 |     Fabrizio Mazzonna and Franco Peracchi    摘要 |           我们调查了老年人是否正确地感知了他们的认知能力下降以及误解的潜在经济后果。首先，我们发现老年人往往低估了他们的认知能力下降。然后我们发现，那些经历了严重衰退但没有意识到的人更有可能遭受财富损失。这些损失在很大程度上反映了金融财富的减少，主要是以前活跃在股市上的富人所经历的。我们的研究结果支持这样一种观点，即没有意识到自己认知能力下降的老年人的经济损失是糟糕的财务决策的结果，而不是理性的撤资策略。         02         再分配分配机制         作者 |     Mohammad Akbarpour, Piotr Dworczak, and Scott Duke Kominers    摘要 |           许多稀缺的公共资源是以低于市场结算价格分配的，有时是免费的。这种“非市场”机制牺牲了一些盈余，但它们有可能提高公平性。我们开发了一个具有再分配关注的机制设计模型。代理商的特点是私下观察到的为质量付费的意愿、公开观察到的标签和社会福利权重。市场设计者控制一组异质质量对象的分配和定价，并最大化福利函数的期望。设计者没有直接观察个人的社会福利权重。我们得出了关于最优机制形式的结构性见解，从而形成了一个确定如何以及何时使用非市场机制的框架。         03         家庭生产中未观察到的投入         作者 |     Sergey Mityakov and Thomas A. Mroz    摘要 |           大多数家庭生产研究忽略了未观察到的投入。然而，如果没有额外的假设，由于未观测到的投入的污染变化，观测到的输入的估计影响无法提供边际产品的信息估计。甚至连边际影响的迹象都无法确定。通过在分析中包括有关非生产性（纯消费）商品的详细信息，可以确定这些偏差的方向，并显著减少偏差。先前需求研究的估计也有助于确定偏差的方向。我们描述了在缺乏此类额外信息的情况下必须援引的严格假设，以便能够将估计的影响与真实的边际产品联系起来。         04         住房供应的微观地理学         作者 |     Nathaniel Baum-Snow and Lu Han    摘要 |           我们对住房供应进行了全面的邻里层面分析。使用我们的估计对美国所有城市社区的占地面积和住房单位供应弹性的预测平均为0.5和0.3，显示出城市内部比城市之间更大的变化。新建工程约占单位供应响应的50%，在拆除和翻新方面发挥着重要的额外作用。供应反应随着中央商务区的发展而增长，主要是与未开发土地、平坦土地和较少监管的日益增加相距甚远。识别来自通勤目的地劳动力需求冲击的变化，这是使用定量空间平衡模型的见解进行汇总的。         05         套利的价值         作者 |     Eduardo Dávila, Daniel Graves, and Cecilia Parlatore    摘要 |           本文研究了金融市场收盘价差的社会价值。我们证明了套利缺口恰好对应于执行套利交易的边际社会价值。此外，套利缺口和价格影响指标足以计算弥合套利缺口的总社会价值，套利缺口可能因不同原因出现，包括持有特定资产的非货币利益。理论上，我们表明，对于给定的套利缺口，在流动性更强的市场中，套利的总社会价值更高。我们计算了弥补利率平价违规的套利缺口所带来的福利收益。         06         企业职业：能力学习与人力资本获取的作用         作者 |     Elena Pastorino    摘要 |           工作和工资的流动性可能源于公司和工人对工人能力的了解，也可能源于工人获得有经验的人力资本。迄今为止，这两个机制的相对重要性一直存在争议。使用一家公司的管理数据，我估计了一个将它们整合在一起的结构模型。我发现现有工作所关注的关于能力的信念对工资的直接影响很小。然而，通过改进员工对公司工作的分类，了解能力间接成为工资增长和分散的关键决定因素。         07         外债、资本管制和二级市场：来自纳粹德国的理论和证据         作者 |     Andrea Papadia and Claudio A. Schioppa    摘要 |           我们研究了内部分配动机如何影响一项重要宏观经济政策的实施：资本控制。为了做到这一点，我们研究了20世纪30年代德国在严格的资本控制下发生的历史上最大的债务遣返之一，提供了丰富的数量和历史证据。我们表明，当局严格控制私人遣返，从而避免了不利的宏观经济影响，同时允许自由遣返，以获得内部政治利益。我们在一个模型中正式化了这一机制，在该模型中，精英捕获可以影响资本控制下的最佳债务遣返和官方储备管理。         08         儿童保育市场、父母劳动力供应和儿童发展         作者 |     Samuel Berlinski, Maria Marta Ferreyra, Luca Flabbi, and Juan David Martin    摘要 |           我们开发并估计了儿童保育的供需模型。在需求方面，家庭做出消费、劳动力供应和育儿的决定。在供应方面，中心做出准入、价格和质量决策。此外，还提供带薪和非正式护理人员。儿童的发展取决于与父母和非租赁护理提供者相处的时间。我们使用来自幼儿纵向研究、出生队列的数据来估计模型，并进行政策实验。只有在高质量的中心或在职母亲才能使用的代金券尤其有效，因为它们在增加母亲劳动力供应的同时，还能促进儿童发展。    </content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.econdiy.wiki/jpe/JPE_CN_Volume 132, Number 60006</guid></item><item><title>aer/AER_issues_764</title><description>none</description><content:encoded>输 Front Matter   Nobel Lecture: An Evolving Economic Force   Local Economic and Political Effects of Trade Deals: Evidence from NAFTA   Status Externalities in Education and Low Birth Rates in Korea   Welfare Comparisons for Biased Learning   The Flight to Safety and International Risk Sharing   Long-Run Effects of Incentivizing Work after Childbirth   Task-Based Discrimination   Information Technology and Returns to Scale   Breaking Gender Barriers: Experimental Evidence on Men in Pink-Collar Jobs   Financial Access and Labor Market Outcomes: Evidence from Credit Lotteries       01         Front Matter         作者 |         摘要 |           Why have white, less-educated voters left the Democratic Party? We highlight the role of the 1994 North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA). In event-study analysis, we demonstrate that counties whose 1990 employment depended on industries vulnerable to NAFTA suffered large and persistent employment losses after its implementation. Voters in these counties (and protectionist voters regardless of geography) turned away from the party of President Clinton, who promoted the agreement. This shift is larger for whites (especially men and those without a college degree) and social conservatives, suggesting that racial identity and social-issue positions mediate reactions to economic policies.         02         Nobel Lecture: An Evolving Economic Force         作者 |     Claudia Goldin    摘要 |           South Koreans appear to be preoccupied with their offspring's education and also have the lowest total fertility rate in the world. We propose a novel theory with status externalities and endogenous fertility connecting these facts, motivated by novel empirical evidence on private education spillovers. Using a quantitative model calibrated to Korea, we find that fertility would be 28 percent higher without the externality. We explore the effects of government policy: a pro-natal transfer or an education tax can increase fertility and reduce education spending. An education tax of 22 percent together with moderate pro-natal transfers maximizes the current generation's welfare.         03         Local Economic and Political Effects of Trade Deals: Evidence from NAFTA         作者 |     Jiwon Choi, Ilyana Kuziemko, Ebonya Washington, Gavin Wright    摘要 |           We study robust welfare comparisons of learning biases (misspecified Bayesian and some forms of non-Bayesian updating). Given a true signal distribution, we deem one bias more harmful than another if it yields lower objective expected payoffs in all decision problems. We characterize this ranking in static and dynamic settings. While the static characterization compares posteriors signal by signal, the dynamic characterization employs an "efficiency index" measuring how fast beliefs converge. We quantify and compare the severity of several well-documented biases. We also highlight disagreements between the static and dynamic rankings, and that some "large" biases dynamically outperform other "vanishingly small" biases.         04         Status Externalities in Education and Low Birth Rates in Korea         作者 |     Seongeun Kim, Minchul Yum    摘要 |           We study a business cycle model of the international monetary system featuring a time varying demand for safe dollar bonds, greater risk-bearing capacity in the United States than the rest of the world, and nominal rigidities. A flight to safety generates a dollar appreciation and decline in global output. Dollar bonds thus command a negative risk premium, and the United States holds a levered portfolio of capital finances in dollars. We quantify the effects of safety shocks and heterogeneity in risk-bearing capacity for global macroeconomic volatility, US external adjustment, and policy transmission, as of dollar swap lines.         05         Welfare Comparisons for Biased Learning         作者 |     Mira Frick, Ryota Iijima, Yuhta Ishii    摘要 |           This paper identifies the impact of increasing post-childbirth work incentives on mothers' long-run careers. We exploit variation in work incentives across mothers based on the timing of a first birth and eligibility for the 1993 expansion of the Earned Income Tax Credit. Ten to nineteen years after a first birth, single mothers who were exposed to the expansion immediately after birth ("early"), rather than 3–6 years later ("late"), have 0.62 more years of work experience and 4.2 percent higher earnings conditional on working. We show that higher earnings are primarily explained by improved wages due to greater work experience.         06         The Flight to Safety and International Risk Sharing         作者 |     Rohan Kekre, Moritz Lenel    摘要 |           We develop a task-based model of occupational sorting to identify and quantify the effect of discrimination, racial skill gaps, and aggregate task prices on Black-White differences in labor market outcomes over time. At the heart of our framework is the idea that the size and nature of racial barriers faced by Black workers vary by the task requirements of each job. We define a new task that measures the extent to which individuals interact with others as part of their job. We show that this measure is a good proxy for the extent of discrimination in the economy.         07         Long-Run Effects of Incentivizing Work after Childbirth         作者 |     Elira Kuka, ama Shenhav    摘要 |           What are the implications of the dramatic fall in IT prices for aggregate technology? When firm-level technologies are continuously differentiable, a factor price shock leads to (i) a substitution between factors and/or (ii) an endogenous response of returns to scale. The second channel is governed by the output elasticity of relative factor demand. Using detailed firm-level data from France, we estimate this elasticity to be positive for IT factor demand. A quantitative exercise accounting for both technological channels shows that falling IT prices can explain much of the changes in concentration and the composition of aggregate labor share in France.         08         Task-Based Discrimination         作者 |     Erik Hurst, Yona Rubinstein, Kazuatsu Shimizu    摘要 |           I investigate men's limited entry into female-dominated sectors through a large-scale field experiment. The design exogenously varies recruitment messages by showing photographs of current workers (male or female) and providing information on the share of workers who received high evaluations in the past (higher or lower). A male photograph has no impact on men's applications, but informing about a lower share of high evaluations encourages men to apply and enables the employer to hire and retain more talented men. The impact of this informational intervention remains positive for the employer also accounting for its effects on female applicants and hires.         09         Information Technology and Returns to Scale         作者 |     Danial Lashkari, Arthur Bauer, Jocelyn Boussard    摘要 |           We assess the employment and income effects of access to credit dedicated to investment in individual mobility by exploiting time-series variation in access to credit through lotteries for participants in a group-lending mechanism in Brazil. We find that access to credit for investment in individual mobility increases formal employment rates and salaries, yielding an annual rate of return of 12 to 15 percent. Consistent with a geographically broader job search, individuals transition to jobs farther from home and public transportation. Our results suggest that accessing distant labor markets through credit for investment in individual mobility yields high and persistent returns.    </content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.econdiy.wiki/aer/AER_issues_7640005</guid></item><item><title>jpe/JPE_CN_issues_764</title><description>none</description><content:encoded>输 诺贝尔演讲：一股不断发展的经济力量   贸易协议对地方经济和政治的影响：来自北美自由贸易协定的证据   韩国教育的地位外部性与低出生率   有偏见学习的福利比较   安全飞行与国际风险分担   生育后工作激励的长期效应   基于任务的歧视   信息技术与规模回报   打破性别障碍：对从事粉领工作的男性的实验证据   金融准入和劳动力市场结果：来自信用彩票的证据       01         诺贝尔演讲：一股不断发展的经济力量         作者 |         摘要 |           为什么受教育程度较低的白人选民离开了民主党？我们强调1994年《北美自由贸易协定》的作用。在事件研究分析中，我们证明，1990年就业依赖于易受北美自由贸易协定影响的行业的县在实施后遭受了巨大而持续的就业损失。这些县的选民（以及不分地理位置的保护主义选民）拒绝了推动该协议的克林顿总统的政党。这种转变对白人（尤其是男性和没有大学学历的人）和社会保守派来说更大，这表明种族认同和社会问题立场会调节对经济政策的反应。         02         贸易协议对地方经济和政治的影响：来自北美自由贸易协定的证据         作者 |     Claudia Goldin    摘要 |           韩国人似乎专注于子女的教育，而且总生育率也是世界上最低的。我们提出了一个新的理论，将这些事实与地位外部性和内生生育率联系起来，其动机是关于私立教育溢出的新的经验证据。使用一个针对韩国的定量模型，我们发现如果没有外部性，生育率将高出28%。我们探讨了政府政策的影响：产前转移或教育税可以提高生育率并减少教育支出。22%的教育税加上适度的产前转移，最大限度地提高了这一代人的福利。         03         韩国教育的地位外部性与低出生率         作者 |     Jiwon Choi, Ilyana Kuziemko, Ebonya Washington, Gavin Wright    摘要 |           我们研究了学习偏差的稳健福利比较（指定错误的贝叶斯和某些形式的非贝叶斯更新）。给定真实的信号分布，如果在所有决策问题中产生较低的客观预期收益，我们认为一种偏差比另一种更有害。我们在静态和动态设置中描述这种排名。当静态表征逐个信号比较后验信号时，动态表征采用了一个“效率指数”来衡量信念收敛的速度。我们量化并比较了几个有充分记录的偏差的严重程度。我们还强调了静态和动态排名之间的差异，以及一些“大”的偏见在动态上胜过其他“微不足道”的偏见。         04         有偏见学习的福利比较         作者 |     Seongeun Kim, Minchul Yum    摘要 |           我们研究了一个国际货币体系的商业周期模型，其特征是对安全美元债券的需求随时间变化，美国的风险承受能力高于世界其他地区，以及名义刚性。向安全地带的逃亡导致美元升值，全球产出下降。因此，美元债券的风险溢价为负，美国持有以美元为单位的杠杆资本金融投资组合。我们量化了安全冲击和风险承受能力异质性对全球宏观经济波动、美国外部调整和政策传导的影响，如美元互换额度。         05         安全飞行与国际风险分担         作者 |     Mira Frick, Ryota Iijima, Yuhta Ishii    摘要 |           本文确定了增加产后工作激励对母亲长期职业生涯的影响。我们根据初产的时间和1993年扩大劳动所得税抵免的资格，利用了母亲之间工作激励的差异。第一次分娩后10至19年，出生后立即（“早期”）而不是3-6年后（“晚期”）暴露于扩张的单身母亲，有0.62年的工作经验，以工作为条件的收入高4.2%。我们发现，收入的增加主要是由于工作经验的增加而导致工资的提高。         06         生育后工作激励的长期效应         作者 |     Rohan Kekre, Moritz Lenel    摘要 |           我们开发了一个基于任务的职业分类模型，以确定和量化歧视、种族技能差距和总任务价格对劳动力市场结果随时间变化的黑人-白人差异的影响。我们框架的核心是黑人工人面临的种族障碍的大小和性质因每项工作的任务要求而异。我们定义了一项新任务，衡量个人在工作中与他人互动的程度。我们表明，这项措施很好地反映了经济中歧视的程度。         07         基于任务的歧视         作者 |     Elira Kuka, ama Shenhav    摘要 |           IT价格的大幅下跌对聚合技术有什么影响？当企业层面的技术持续可微分时，要素价格冲击会导致（i）要素之间的替代和/或（ii）规模回报的内生反应。第二个渠道由相对要素需求的产出弹性决定。利用法国公司层面的详细数据，我们估计这种弹性对IT要素需求是正的。对这两种技术渠道的定量分析表明，IT价格的下跌可以解释法国劳动力集中度和总份额构成的大部分变化。         08         信息技术与规模回报         作者 |     Erik Hurst, Yona Rubinstein, Kazuatsu Shimizu    摘要 |           我通过一项大规模的实地实验，调查了男性有限地进入女性主导的行业。该设计通过展示当前工人（男性或女性）的照片和提供过去获得高评价（较高或较低）的工人比例的信息，从外部改变了招聘信息。男性照片对男性的申请没有影响，但告知较高评价的比例较低会鼓励男性申请，并使雇主能够雇佣和留住更多有才华的男性。这种信息干预对雇主的影响仍然是积极的，也说明了它对女性申请人和雇员的影响。         09         打破性别障碍：对从事粉领工作的男性的实验证据         作者 |     Danial Lashkari, Arthur Bauer, Jocelyn Boussard    摘要 |           我们通过利用巴西团体贷款机制参与者通过彩票获得信贷的时间序列变化，评估了专门用于个人流动性投资的信贷对就业和收入的影响。我们发现，获得信贷用于个人流动性投资会提高正式就业率和工资，年回报率为12%至15%。与地理范围更广的求职相一致，个人会过渡到离家和公共交通更远的工作。我们的研究结果表明，通过个人流动性投资信贷进入遥远的劳动力市场会产生高而持久的回报。    </content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.econdiy.wiki/jpe/JPE_CN_issues_7640004</guid></item><item><title>jpe/JPE_CN_issues_764</title><description>none</description><content:encoded>输 诺贝尔演讲：一股不断发展的经济力量   贸易协议对地方经济和政治的影响：来自北美自由贸易协定的证据   韩国教育的地位外部性与低出生率   有偏见学习的福利比较   安全飞行与国际风险分担   生育后工作激励的长期效应   基于任务的歧视   信息技术与规模回报   打破性别障碍：对从事粉领工作的男性的实验证据   金融准入和劳动力市场结果：来自信用彩票的证据       01         诺贝尔演讲：一股不断发展的经济力量         作者 |         摘要 |           为什么受教育程度较低的白人选民离开了民主党？我们强调1994年《北美自由贸易协定》的作用。在事件研究分析中，我们证明，1990年就业依赖于易受北美自由贸易协定影响的行业的县在实施后遭受了巨大而持续的就业损失。这些县的选民（以及不分地理位置的保护主义选民）拒绝了推动该协议的克林顿总统的政党。这种转变对白人（尤其是男性和没有大学学历的人）和社会保守派来说更大，这表明种族认同和社会问题立场会调节对经济政策的反应。         02         贸易协议对地方经济和政治的影响：来自北美自由贸易协定的证据         作者 |     Claudia Goldin    摘要 |           韩国人似乎专注于子女的教育，而且总生育率也是世界上最低的。我们提出了一个新的理论，将这些事实与地位外部性和内生生育率联系起来，其动机是关于私立教育溢出的新的经验证据。使用一个针对韩国的定量模型，我们发现如果没有外部性，生育率将高出28%。我们探讨了政府政策的影响：产前转移或教育税可以提高生育率并减少教育支出。22%的教育税加上适度的产前转移，最大限度地提高了这一代人的福利。         03         韩国教育的地位外部性与低出生率         作者 |     Jiwon Choi, Ilyana Kuziemko, Ebonya Washington, Gavin Wright    摘要 |           我们研究了学习偏差的稳健福利比较（指定错误的贝叶斯和某些形式的非贝叶斯更新）。给定真实的信号分布，如果在所有决策问题中产生较低的客观预期收益，我们认为一种偏差比另一种更有害。我们在静态和动态设置中描述这种排名。当静态表征逐个信号比较后验信号时，动态表征采用了一个“效率指数”来衡量信念收敛的速度。我们量化并比较了几个有充分记录的偏差的严重程度。我们还强调了静态和动态排名之间的差异，以及一些“大”的偏见在动态上胜过其他“微不足道”的偏见。         04         有偏见学习的福利比较         作者 |     Seongeun Kim, Minchul Yum    摘要 |           我们研究了一个国际货币体系的商业周期模型，其特征是对安全美元债券的需求随时间变化，美国的风险承受能力高于世界其他地区，以及名义刚性。向安全地带的逃亡导致美元升值，全球产出下降。因此，美元债券的风险溢价为负，美国持有以美元为单位的杠杆资本金融投资组合。我们量化了安全冲击和风险承受能力异质性对全球宏观经济波动、美国外部调整和政策传导的影响，如美元互换额度。         05         安全飞行与国际风险分担         作者 |     Mira Frick, Ryota Iijima, Yuhta Ishii    摘要 |           本文确定了增加产后工作激励对母亲长期职业生涯的影响。我们根据初产的时间和1993年扩大劳动所得税抵免的资格，利用了母亲之间工作激励的差异。第一次分娩后10至19年，出生后立即（“早期”）而不是3-6年后（“晚期”）暴露于扩张的单身母亲，有0.62年的工作经验，以工作为条件的收入高4.2%。我们发现，收入的增加主要是由于工作经验的增加而导致工资的提高。         06         生育后工作激励的长期效应         作者 |     Rohan Kekre, Moritz Lenel    摘要 |           我们开发了一个基于任务的职业分类模型，以确定和量化歧视、种族技能差距和总任务价格对劳动力市场结果随时间变化的黑人-白人差异的影响。我们框架的核心是黑人工人面临的种族障碍的大小和性质因每项工作的任务要求而异。我们定义了一项新任务，衡量个人在工作中与他人互动的程度。我们表明，这项措施很好地反映了经济中歧视的程度。         07         基于任务的歧视         作者 |     Elira Kuka, ama Shenhav    摘要 |           IT价格的大幅下跌对聚合技术有什么影响？当企业层面的技术持续可微分时，要素价格冲击会导致（i）要素之间的替代和/或（ii）规模回报的内生反应。第二个渠道由相对要素需求的产出弹性决定。利用法国公司层面的详细数据，我们估计这种弹性对IT要素需求是正的。对这两种技术渠道的定量分析表明，IT价格的下跌可以解释法国劳动力集中度和总份额构成的大部分变化。         08         信息技术与规模回报         作者 |     Erik Hurst, Yona Rubinstein, Kazuatsu Shimizu    摘要 |           我通过一项大规模的实地实验，调查了男性有限地进入女性主导的行业。该设计通过展示当前工人（男性或女性）的照片和提供过去获得高评价（较高或较低）的工人比例的信息，从外部改变了招聘信息。男性照片对男性的申请没有影响，但告知较高评价的比例较低会鼓励男性申请，并使雇主能够雇佣和留住更多有才华的男性。这种信息干预对雇主的影响仍然是积极的，也说明了它对女性申请人和雇员的影响。         09         打破性别障碍：对从事粉领工作的男性的实验证据         作者 |     Danial Lashkari, Arthur Bauer, Jocelyn Boussard    摘要 |           我们通过利用巴西团体贷款机制参与者通过彩票获得信贷的时间序列变化，评估了专门用于个人流动性投资的信贷对就业和收入的影响。我们发现，获得信贷用于个人流动性投资会提高正式就业率和工资，年回报率为12%至15%。与地理范围更广的求职相一致，个人会过渡到离家和公共交通更远的工作。我们的研究结果表明，通过个人流动性投资信贷进入遥远的劳动力市场会产生高而持久的回报。    </content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.econdiy.wiki/jpe/JPE_CN_issues_7640003</guid></item><item><title>jle/JLE_Vol 42, No 3</title><description>none</description><content:encoded>输 The Effect of Job Search Requirements on Family Welfare Receipt   The Decline in Rent Sharing   Who Benefits from Attending Effective High Schools?   School Performance, Score Inflation, and Neighborhood Development   The Speed of Earnings Responses to Taxation and the Role of Firm Labor Demand   Industry Mix, Local Labor Markets, and the Incidence of Trade Shocks   Cohort Size and the Marriage Market: Explaining Nearly a Century of Changes in US Marriage Rates       01         The Effect of Job Search Requirements on Family Welfare Receipt         作者 |     Marc K. ChanNicolas HéraultHa VuRoger Wilkins    摘要 |           Many countries impose job search requirements on unemployment benefit recipients. Existing studies have mainly focused on the impact of incremental changes to requirements on the recipients. Australian reforms in 1995 saw groups of partnered welfare recipients newly subjected to job search requirements, allowing us to produce causal estimates of the effects on family welfare receipt of introducing such requirements. Using a quasi-experimental design and administrative data, we find large negative effects on welfare receipt for the mature-age partnered women targeted by the reforms and similar effects on welfare receipt of their partners, suggesting that family labor supply decisions were considerably affected.         02         The Decline in Rent Sharing         作者 |     Brian BellPaweł BukowskiStephen Machin    摘要 |           The evolution of rent sharing is studied. Based on a panel of the top 300 publicly quoted British companies over 35 years and using excess stock market returns to patenting activity as an instrument for economic rents, the paper reports evidence of a significant fall over time in the pass-through from rents to wages. It confirms that wages do respond to firm-level shocks to economic rents, but by significantly less after 2000 than during the 1980s and 1990s. The evidence of decline is robust, corroborated with alternative instruments and industry-level analysis for the United States and the European Union.         03         Who Benefits from Attending Effective High Schools?         作者 |     C. Kirabo JacksonSebastián KiguelShanette C. PorterJohn Q. Easton    摘要 |           We estimate the longer-run effects of attending an effective high school (one that improves a combination of test scores, survey measures of socioemotional development, and behaviors in ninth grade) for students who are more versus less educationally advantaged. All students benefit from attending effective schools, but the least advantaged students experience larger improvements in high school graduation, college going, and school-based arrests. Test score value-added understates the long-run importance of effective schools, particularly for less advantaged populations. Patterns suggest that this may, in part, reflect less advantaged students being relatively more responsive to non-test-score dimensions of school quality.         04         School Performance, Score Inflation, and Neighborhood Development         作者 |     Erich BattistinLorenzo Neri    摘要 |           We show that score inflation yields residential sorting around what households expect to be better schools, with long-term consequences for the economic geography of neighborhoods. We consider primary school exams in England, where grading standards have triggered an inflation of indicators in the national performance tables since the mid-1990s. Local neighborhoods were gentrified because of school improvements artificially signaled by score inflation. Competition between schools increased, yielding a real improvement in their quality. Effects of score inflation on house prices, deprivation, and local economic activities are identifiable through to the present day.         05         The Speed of Earnings Responses to Taxation and the Role of Firm Labor Demand         作者 |     Matthew GudgeonSimon Trenkle    摘要 |           This paper studies the speed at which workers’ pretax earnings respond to tax changes along the intensive margin. We do so in the context of Germany, where a large notch in the tax schedule induces sharp bunching in the earnings distribution. We analyze earnings responses to two policy reforms that shift this notch outward and find clear evidence that frictions delay the earnings responses of more than 38% of workers. We propose that heterogeneity in firm labor demand plays a key role in generating the observed differences in the speed of workers’ earnings responses and provide supporting evidence.         06         Industry Mix, Local Labor Markets, and the Incidence of Trade Shocks         作者 |     Moises YiSteffen MuellerJens Stegmaier    摘要 |           We analyze how skill transferability and the local industry mix affect the adjustment costs of workers hit by a trade shock. Using German administrative data and novel measures of economic distance, we construct an index of labor market absorptiveness that captures the degree to which workers from a particular industry are able to reallocate into other jobs. Among manufacturing workers, we find that the earnings loss associated with increased import exposure is much higher for those who live in the least absorptive regions. We conclude that the local industry composition plays an important role in the adjustment processes of workers.         07         Cohort Size and the Marriage Market: Explaining Nearly a Century of Changes in US Marriage Rates         作者 |     Mary Ann BronsonMaurizio Mazzocco    摘要 |           We document that the US marriage market is characterized by two systematic empirical patterns. First, there is a quantitatively large, strong, and persistent negative relationship between changes in cohort size and marriage rates of women. Second, the same negative correlation holds for men. We then establish the features a model should possess to generate these patterns. A standard matching model with search frictions is rejected by the data because it produces a negative relationship for women but a positive relationship for men. We generalize the standard model to show under what conditions it rationalizes both patterns.    </content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.econdiy.wiki/jle/JLE_Vol 42, No 30002</guid></item><item><title>jle/JLE_CN_Vol 42, No 3</title><description>none</description><content:encoded>输 求职要求对家庭福利收入的影响   租金分摊的下降   谁能从有效的高中学习中受益？   学校表现、分数膨胀与社区发展   收入对税收的反应速度与企业劳动力需求的作用   行业结构、当地劳动力市场和贸易冲击的发生率   队列规模与婚姻市场：解释美国结婚率近一个世纪的变化       01         求职要求对家庭福利收入的影响         作者 |     Marc K. ChanNicolas HéraultHa VuRoger Wilkins    摘要 |           许多国家对失业救济金领取者提出求职要求。现有的研究主要集中在需求的增量变化对接受者的影响上。1995年澳大利亚的改革使合作福利领取者群体新受到求职要求的约束，使我们能够对引入此类要求对家庭福利领取的影响进行因果估计。使用准实验设计和行政数据，我们发现改革所针对的成年伴侣妇女的福利待遇受到了巨大的负面影响，而她们的伴侣的福利待遇也受到了类似的影响，这表明家庭劳动力供应决策受到了相当大的影响。         02         租金分摊的下降         作者 |     Brian BellPaweł BukowskiStephen Machin    摘要 |           研究了租金分摊的演变过程。该论文基于一个由35年来前300家公开上市的英国公司组成的小组，并利用超额的股票市场回报作为经济租金的工具，报告了从租金到工资的传递随着时间的推移显著下降的证据。它证实，工资确实对企业层面的经济租金冲击做出了反应，但在2000年之后的反应明显低于20世纪80年代和90年代。美国和欧盟的替代工具和行业层面的分析证实了下降的有力证据。         03         谁能从有效的高中学习中受益？         作者 |     C. Kirabo JacksonSebastián KiguelShanette C. PorterJohn Q. Easton    摘要 |           我们估计了上一所有效的高中（这所高中提高了九年级的考试成绩、社会情绪发展调查指标和行为的组合）对教育优势较大和较差的学生的长期影响。所有学生都能从有效的学校中受益，但最弱势的学生在高中毕业、上大学和学校逮捕方面都有更大的进步。考试成绩增值低估了有效学校的长期重要性，尤其是对弱势群体而言。模式表明，这可能在一定程度上反映出优势较差的学生对学校质量的非测试分数维度相对更敏感。         04         学校表现、分数膨胀与社区发展         作者 |     Erich BattistinLorenzo Neri    摘要 |           我们表明，分数通胀会产生围绕家庭期望的更好学校的住宅分类，这会对社区的经济地理产生长期影响。我们以英国的小学考试为例，自20世纪90年代中期以来，英国的评分标准引发了国家成绩表指标的膨胀。由于分数膨胀人为地标志着学校的改善，当地社区被绅士化了。学校之间的竞争加剧，使学校的质量得到了真正的提高。分数膨胀对房价、贫困和当地经济活动的影响直到今天都是可以识别的。         05         收入对税收的反应速度与企业劳动力需求的作用         作者 |     Matthew GudgeonSimon Trenkle    摘要 |           本文研究了工人税前收入对密集边际税收变化的反应速度。我们这样做是在德国的背景下进行的，在德国，税收计划的大幅削减会导致收入分配的急剧集中。我们分析了两项政策改革对收入的反应，这两项改革将收入水平向外转移，并发现了明确的证据表明，摩擦推迟了超过38%的工人的收入反应。我们提出，企业劳动力需求的异质性在产生观察到的工人收入反应速度差异中起着关键作用，并提供了支持性证据。         06         行业结构、当地劳动力市场和贸易冲击的发生率         作者 |     Moises YiSteffen MuellerJens Stegmaier    摘要 |           我们分析了技能转移性和当地产业结构如何影响受贸易冲击影响的工人的调整成本。利用德国的行政数据和新的经济距离衡量标准，我们构建了一个劳动力市场吸收率指数，该指数反映了特定行业的工人能够重新分配到其他工作岗位的程度。在制造业工人中，我们发现，对于那些生活在吸收能力最低地区的人来说，与进口敞口增加相关的收入损失要高得多。我们得出结论，地方产业结构在工人的调整过程中起着重要作用。         07         队列规模与婚姻市场：解释美国结婚率近一个世纪的变化         作者 |     Mary Ann BronsonMaurizio Mazzocco    摘要 |           我们记录了美国婚姻市场有两个系统的经验模式。首先，队列规模的变化与女性结婚率之间存在着巨大、强烈和持久的负相关关系。其次，同样的负相关性也适用于男性。然后，我们建立一个模型应该具有的特征来生成这些模式。具有搜索摩擦的标准匹配模型被数据拒绝，因为它对女性产生了负面关系，但对男性产生了正面关系。我们推广了标准模型，以显示它在什么条件下使这两种模式合理化。    </content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.econdiy.wiki/jle/JLE_CN_Vol 42, No 30001</guid></item><item><title>jle/JLE_CN_Vol 42, No 3</title><description>none</description><content:encoded>输 求职要求对家庭福利收入的影响   租金分摊的下降   谁能从有效的高中学习中受益？   学校表现、分数膨胀与社区发展   收入对税收的反应速度与企业劳动力需求的作用   行业结构、当地劳动力市场和贸易冲击的发生率   队列规模与婚姻市场：解释美国结婚率近一个世纪的变化       01         求职要求对家庭福利收入的影响         作者 |     Marc K. ChanNicolas HéraultHa VuRoger Wilkins    摘要 |           许多国家对失业救济金领取者提出求职要求。现有的研究主要集中在需求的增量变化对接受者的影响上。1995年澳大利亚的改革使合作福利领取者群体新受到求职要求的约束，使我们能够对引入此类要求对家庭福利领取的影响进行因果估计。使用准实验设计和行政数据，我们发现改革所针对的成年伴侣妇女的福利待遇受到了巨大的负面影响，而她们的伴侣的福利待遇也受到了类似的影响，这表明家庭劳动力供应决策受到了相当大的影响。         02         租金分摊的下降         作者 |     Brian BellPaweł BukowskiStephen Machin    摘要 |           研究了租金分摊的演变过程。该论文基于一个由35年来前300家公开上市的英国公司组成的小组，并利用超额的股票市场回报作为经济租金的工具，报告了从租金到工资的传递随着时间的推移显著下降的证据。它证实，工资确实对企业层面的经济租金冲击做出了反应，但在2000年之后的反应明显低于20世纪80年代和90年代。美国和欧盟的替代工具和行业层面的分析证实了下降的有力证据。         03         谁能从有效的高中学习中受益？         作者 |     C. Kirabo JacksonSebastián KiguelShanette C. PorterJohn Q. Easton    摘要 |           我们估计了上一所有效的高中（这所高中提高了九年级的考试成绩、社会情绪发展调查指标和行为的组合）对教育优势较大和较差的学生的长期影响。所有学生都能从有效的学校中受益，但最弱势的学生在高中毕业、上大学和学校逮捕方面都有更大的进步。考试成绩增值低估了有效学校的长期重要性，尤其是对弱势群体而言。模式表明，这可能在一定程度上反映出优势较差的学生对学校质量的非测试分数维度相对更敏感。         04         学校表现、分数膨胀与社区发展         作者 |     Erich BattistinLorenzo Neri    摘要 |           我们表明，分数通胀会产生围绕家庭期望的更好学校的住宅分类，这会对社区的经济地理产生长期影响。我们以英国的小学考试为例，自20世纪90年代中期以来，英国的评分标准引发了国家成绩表指标的膨胀。由于分数膨胀人为地标志着学校的改善，当地社区被绅士化了。学校之间的竞争加剧，使学校的质量得到了真正的提高。分数膨胀对房价、贫困和当地经济活动的影响直到今天都是可以识别的。         05         收入对税收的反应速度与企业劳动力需求的作用         作者 |     Matthew GudgeonSimon Trenkle    摘要 |           本文研究了工人税前收入对密集边际税收变化的反应速度。我们这样做是在德国的背景下进行的，在德国，税收计划的大幅削减会导致收入分配的急剧集中。我们分析了两项政策改革对收入的反应，这两项改革将收入水平向外转移，并发现了明确的证据表明，摩擦推迟了超过38%的工人的收入反应。我们提出，企业劳动力需求的异质性在产生观察到的工人收入反应速度差异中起着关键作用，并提供了支持性证据。         06         行业结构、当地劳动力市场和贸易冲击的发生率         作者 |     Moises YiSteffen MuellerJens Stegmaier    摘要 |           我们分析了技能转移性和当地产业结构如何影响受贸易冲击影响的工人的调整成本。利用德国的行政数据和新的经济距离衡量标准，我们构建了一个劳动力市场吸收率指数，该指数反映了特定行业的工人能够重新分配到其他工作岗位的程度。在制造业工人中，我们发现，对于那些生活在吸收能力最低地区的人来说，与进口敞口增加相关的收入损失要高得多。我们得出结论，地方产业结构在工人的调整过程中起着重要作用。         07         队列规模与婚姻市场：解释美国结婚率近一个世纪的变化         作者 |     Mary Ann BronsonMaurizio Mazzocco    摘要 |           我们记录了美国婚姻市场有两个系统的经验模式。首先，队列规模的变化与女性结婚率之间存在着巨大、强烈和持久的负相关关系。其次，同样的负相关性也适用于男性。然后，我们建立一个模型应该具有的特征来生成这些模式。具有搜索摩擦的标准匹配模型被数据拒绝，因为它对女性产生了负面关系，但对男性产生了正面关系。我们推广了标准模型，以显示它在什么条件下使这两种模式合理化。    </content:encoded><guid isPermaLink="false">https://www.econdiy.wiki/jle/JLE_CN_Vol 42, No 30000</guid></item></channel></rss>